國家歷史博物館
華盛頓
There it is.
它在這。
What we know is that last night,
據我們所知昨晚，
here at the National Museum in Washington D.C.,
華盛頓國家博物館
an artifact known as one of the infamous crystal skulls
一件臭名昭著的藝術品水晶頭骨
was stolen.
被偷。
This is apparently not the first crystal skull to be taken
這顯然不是第一個水晶頭骨被偷。
and, according to the museum's director,
并且，根據博物館館長所說，
there have been at least six skulls in the past two years
過去兩年已有至少六個頭骨。
from museums and collections from across the globe
從博物館和和全球收藏品
that have disappeared under nefarious circumstances.
不明原因消失。
For CNB News this is Joshua O'Dell.
來自CNB新聞，約書亞奧德爾的報道。
水晶頭骨
庫斯科，秘魯
Senor.
塞納。
Salut.
薩呂。
I assume it's authentic.
我認為它是真實的。
Without a doubt.
毫無疑問。
You see, my employer would be very disappointed
你看，我的雇主會很失望。
if it turned out to be a forgery.
如果它被證明是偽造的。
How did you obtain the artifact?
你是怎么搞到這件藝術品的？
Given the nature of my business,
考慮到我的業務性質，
you can understand why I cannot reveal such details.
你可以理解為什么我不能透露這些細節。
There are strict regulations about the transport
運輸和銷售此類文物
and sale of such antiquities.
大概有嚴格的規定。。
Again, my employer would be very-
再說一次，我的雇主非常希望
Your employer either wants what I have to offer or he does not.
你的老板希望要么我出價要么他不想要。
In which case, I have other buyers to meet.
在這種情況下，我有其他買家要見。
You didn't travel 200 miles up into the Andes
你沒必要行駛200英里到安第斯山脈。
if you had other buyers.
如果你有其他買家。
Then we are ready to do business? Yes?
那么我們準備好談生意了？對不？
When you contacted our representative,
當您聯系您的代表，
your message included a certain purchase price.
您的留言有一定的購買價格。
And I believe the amount was more than fair.
我想那數額比較公道。
As does my employer.
因為確實我的雇主。
Do you have the item with you?
你有你的項目？
I'm not a fool, Mr. Mitchell.
我不是一個傻瓜，米切爾先生。
But it is close by.
但就在附近。
Do you have the money?
帶錢了沒？
I'm not a fool either.
我也不是一個傻瓜。
Follow me.
跟我走。
You going to count it?
要不要點下？
That will not be necessary.
沒必要。
Then, my friend,
那么，我的朋友，
we're finished here.
我們交易完了。
What you have feared has come true.
你擔心的事情已經發生了。
And what have I feared?
我擔心什么？
He's gathering the skulls.
他在收集頭骨。
He understands that together they have power.
他明白那聚集一起可以擁有權力。
Who?
誰？
The rich man.
財主。
The infidel, Hadden.
富人。
He's an old man,
他是一個老人，
a foolish man who is driven by dreams of power
一個受權力夢驅使的無知的人。
derived from the skulls.
來自于頭骨。
He is a dangerous man, you understand?
他是個危險的人，你不懂嗎？
Yes, I understand, but the real danger is that
是的，我明白，但真正的危險是。
without the thirteenth skull
沒有第十三頭骨
there will be no way to control them.
將沒有法來控制它們。
The other twelve could become unstable
其他12個可能變得不穩定。
and cause massive destruction.
并造成大規模破壞。
This is why the brotherhood has given you a task.
這就是兄弟會給你這個任務的原因。
There will be bloodshed.
會有殺戮。
Are you asking me for my approval or my opinion?
你是在征求我的同意還是我的意見？
I don't need your approval.
我不需要你批準。
Then my opinion is that there is no need for violence,
那么我的觀點是沒必要暴力，
he just needs to be stopped.
只是阻止他。
You're a fool to believe a rich man can be stopped
傻瓜才信一個富人會被阻止。
without bloodshed.
而不是通過殺戮。
I understand you have a mission and I wish you good luck,
我知道你有一個使命，我祝你好運，
but don't let your anger poison you, Hussein.
但別讓你的憤怒害了你，侯賽因。
korallgrottan洞穴，瑞典
Check all your equipment.
檢查所有設備。
You sure we have enough rope?
確保我們有足夠長的繩子？
You sure there's something down there?
你肯定東西在那嗎？
I wouldn't be doing this
我不會做。
if I didn't think there was something down there.
如果我不確認東西在下面。
You know how I feel about heights, Terry.
你知道我是怎么想海拔，泰利。
Don't worry about it.
別擔心。
Have I ever let you down?
我何曾讓你失望？
Three, four times, tops.
3，4次，上衣。
Climbing is my business.
登山是我的強項。
You're just gonna have to suck it up.
你只需要別抱怨了。
Look at that, bro.
看看那個，哥哥。
Go easy...
去容易。
...over the lip.
邊上。
Whooo!
呼！
Go steady, bro.
穩住，哥哥。
Look at that!
瞧那個！
Yeah.
耶。
Holy cow.
不會吧。
It was here.
是這里。
Yeah? How can you be so sure?
是嗎？你怎么這么肯定？
This is the last place in his notebook that he visited.
這是他筆記本筆記本里最后參觀的地方。
After living with his obsession with the thirteenth skull
以后的生活與他的癡迷第十三頭骨。
For all these years,
這些年來，
we're finally going to find it.
我們最終會發現它。
After you.
你先。
You're the archaeologist.
你是考古學家。
Well, you're the adventurer.
好了，你是冒險家。
The wife would argue with that.
妻子會認為與該。
She says I'm a glorified tour guide.
她說，我是一個榮耀的導游。
So guide.
洙導游。
Ok, brother.
好吧，哥哥。
There's no GPS down here so I'm working off old maps.
沒有GPS所有我靠老地圖。
It's down this cave another couple hundred meters.
它的下跌這個洞穴另一對夫婦百米。
You sure dad was here?
你肯定爸爸在這里？
He describes this tunnel.
他描述了這條隧道。
For all we know,
我們都知道，
what's left of him is lying around down here somewhere.
什么是留給他的是躺在附近這兒的地方。
We owe it to him to find whatever it was he was after.
我們應該為他找不管它是什么，他是后。
You ready for that?
你準備好了？
I'm ready for that.
我已經準備好了。
You ready for that?
你準備好了？
I guess so.
我猜是。
We'll be alright.
我們會沒事的。
If you say so, brother.
如果你這么說，哥哥。
After you.
你先。
哈登A.G總部
奧地利維也納
Is everything ready?
一切準備好了？
Yes, they've been awaiting your arrival.
是的，他們一直在等待著你的到來。
Any problems?
什么問題？
Me? No.
我呢？沒有。
Bloke I got this from might have a different opinion.
家伙我得到這個從可能有不同的意見。
Why's that?
為什么？
I don't think you want to know that, Ms. Mallory.
我不認為你想知道的是，馬洛里小姐。
The lab has been built eight levels underground.
該實驗室已建成八個級別的地下。
You expecting trouble?
你期待的麻煩？
Let's hope not.
讓我們希望不是。
Watch yourself.
留神。
This way.
這邊。
Watch your feet.
注意腳下。
HEY,
哎，
looks like we found something.
看來，我們發現了一些東西。
We did, didn't we?
確實，不是嗎？
After you.
你先。
Age before beauty.
老人優先。
Is that him?
是他嗎？
You didn't think he'd miss this moment, do you?
你不認為他會錯過這一刻，你呢？
Mr. Hadden?
哈登先生？
Mr. Mitchell.
米切爾先生。
Bravo .
干得好
Thank you, sir.
謝謝你，先生。
I don't know how much time I may have left,
我不知道還能活多久，
so let's not waste any more of it.
所以我們不要再浪費時間了。
Is that normal?
正常嗎？
Well, as far as we're aware,
同時，據我們所知，
this is the first time the skulls have been reunited
這是第一次的頭骨團聚
in the history of mankind.
人類歷史上。
What's happening?
發生了什么？
There's sonic vibration at sixteen hertz.
有聲波振動16赫茲。
I feel a little sick.
我覺得有些不舒服。
I don't know how they're doing it,
我不知道他們是如何做的，
but these things are generating their own magnetic field.
但這些東西都產生自己的磁場。
That's not possible.
這是不可能的。
Tell them that.
告訴他們。
What's it say?
什么好說的？
Thursday night is ladies night.
周四晚上是女士之夜。
All women will be admitted, no cover.
所有的女人都會被錄取，無蓋。
All drinks two shackles.
所有飲料2束縛。
What?
什么？
I have no idea.
我不知道。
But they're in dad's book.
但他們在爸爸的書。
Twelve distinct symbols.
12不同的符號。
How can you know that, smart guy
你怎么能知道，聰明的家伙。
if you don't even know what they say.
如果你不知道他們說什么。
Well, I don't need to be able to translate them
好吧，我并不需要能夠把它們翻譯。
in order to know that is Acadian,
為了知道是阿卡迪亞，
this is Egyptian,
這是埃及，
those over here I don't really recognize.
那些在這里我真的不認識。
This, this looks pre-Colombian.
這一點，這看起來前哥倫布。
Most likely Mayan.
最有可能的瑪雅。
South American?
南美？
What the hell's it doing here?
地獄的是這里做什么？
Exactly.
正是。
Pre-Babylonian, Sumerian, we've got Egyptian, possibly Mayan.
預巴比倫，蘇美爾，我們已經得到了埃及，瑪雅可能。
My guess is it's twelve different groups
我的猜測是它的十二個不同的組。
representing a different early civilization.
代表不同的早期文明。
So what's the thirteenth for?
有啥第十三呢？
I mean, you've got twelve sets of symbols,
我的意思是，你已經有了12組符號，
twelve ancient civilizations, twelve skulls.
12文明古國，12頭骨。
If there really is a thirteenth skull,
如果真的有第十三個頭骨，
what's that about?
那是什么呢？
That, my friend, is a good question.
是，我的朋友，是一個很好的問題。
I really have no idea at this point,
我真的不知道在這一點上，
but I'm sure I'm gonna find out.
但我敢肯定，我會找到了。
I think I'm gonna puke!
我想我會嘔吐！
Yeah, it's the frequency.
是的，它的頻率。
Certain modulations cause nausea.
某些調制引起惡心。
At seven hertz, it can cause your body to come apart
七赫茲，它可能會導致你的身體來分開。
at a nuclear level.
在核級。
Is off the scale!
已關閉的規模！
We're gonna lose it. Clear the room.
我們會失去它。清理房間。
Clear the room!
清理房間！
Get them out of there!
讓他們離開那里！
We've tried to activate the shut-down-
我們試圖激活關閉
Just do what I tell you!
只是做我告訴你！
Whoa.
哇。
What'd you touch?
你摸了什么？
Nothing! I didn't do anything!
沒！我什么都沒做！
I told you not to touch anything!
我告訴你不要碰任何東西！
Wow.
哇。
北約空軍基地
薩拉戈薩,西班牙
Code Level Red
紅色代碼。
Colonel, the pulse has dissipated.
上校，脈沖消散。
Do we have any reports of a nuclear detonation?
我們有一個核爆炸的任何報告？
Negative, sir.
消極的，先生。
Nothing?
什么？
No, sir.
沒有，先生。
Nothing.
沒有。
Satellite or seismic.
衛星或地震。
Then what the hell was it?
那么到底是什么呢？
We've picked up an electro-magnetic burst,
我們挑upan電磁爆，
and it appears it's originated in Vienna.
而且似乎它起源于維也納。
Vienna?
維也納？
Vienna, Austria?
奧地利維也納？
As in Mozart and chocolates?
作為莫扎特和巧克力？
That's correct, sir.
這是正確的，先生。
Alright.
好吧。
Commander of the watch, take us back to yellow.
手表的指揮官，把我們帶回了黃色。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
Electra-magnetic pulses don't just come out of nowhere.
電磁脈沖不只是憑空出現的。
Roger that, sir.
了解，先生。
Major.
主要。
Tell the joint chiefs they'll know what it was when I know what it was.
告訴參謀長聯席會議他們會知道那是什么，當我知道這是什么。
All of it is back to normal except...
這一切恢復正常，除了。
The skulls are still generating a field.
頭骨仍產生一個字段。
Exactly.
正是。
They're holding steady for the moment, but-
他們保持穩定的時刻，按鈕
You saw what happened.
你看到發生了什么。
Yes, of course.
是的，當然。
Well, we knew that the skulls possess unique magnetic qualities.
好了，我們知道，頭骨具有獨特的磁性特質。
If your theory was correct, the thirteenth should have-
如果你的理論是正確的，第十三應該有─
Should have been able to control the others.
本來應該能夠控制他人。
The theory isn't the problem.
理論是沒有問題的。
The problem is that that wasn't the thirteenth skull.
的問題是，這不是第十三顱骨。
You're not blaming this cock-up on me, are you?
你不是在責怪我，他的公雞了，是嗎？
Who exactly should we blame for this unmitigated disaster,
到底誰應該去責備這個不折不扣的災難，
Mr. Mitchell?
先生。米切爾？
Mr. Hadden-
先生。 hadden-
You vouched for the authenticity and you delivered a forgery.
你擔保的真實性，你發表了偽造。
Mr. Hadden, I'm really sorry but in my line of work
先生。哈登，我真的很抱歉，但我的老本行。
people have a tendency to lie.
人有一種傾向，說謊。
Is that so, Mr. Mitchell?
是這樣的，先生。米切爾？
I was going on information supplied by your contacts, sir.
我本來打算由您的聯系人所提供的資料，先生。
Yes, and you were supposed to vet this information, am I correct?
是的，你應該審核這些信息，對嗎？
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
You could have gone and interrogated the chap
你可能已經和審訊的第一章。
who gave it to you, but that would have been too difficult,
誰給你的，但是這將是太困難的，
wouldn't it?
不是嗎？
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
Everybody makes mistakes.
每個人都會犯錯。
Thank you, Mr. Hadden.
謝謝你，哈登先生。
Don't ever make another one.
永遠不要犯同一個錯誤。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
Go and get the real skull.
去找真正的頭骨。
Go with him.
和他一起去。
There isn't a lot of time.
沒多少時間了。
I want the families of those two men who died
我想這死了的兩個男人的家庭。
taken care of.
得到妥善照顧。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
A strange electrical disturbance
一個奇怪的電子干擾。
rocked Vienna, Austria last night
昨晚震動了奧地利維也納。
with power outages...
與停電。
...There was a large blast in the centre of the city...
市中心有一次大爆炸。
...Coming in now, the French NATO troops
目前，駐法國的北約部隊。
high alert following...
處于高度戒備狀態。
...BMP...
BMP
...Any word from city or government officials...
任一個城市或政府官員的任何單詞。
...Have refused to comment on this...
對此拒絕置評。
...Government officials on what has caused this...
政府官員是什么造成了這種。
...Detonation of an atomic weapon...
引爆原子武器。
...What seems to be a high-profile meeting
似乎是一個高調的會議。
with the president...
與總統。
I'm Melanie Cox, live from Vienna, stay with us.
我是梅拉妮·考克斯，維也納在線，和我們呆在一起。
Wow.
哇。
Cool.
酷。
Be careful what you touch, things could be booby-trapped.
小心你碰的，它會殺了你。
Sorry, bro.
對不起，兄弟。
It's dad's ring.
這是爸爸的戒指。
You were right.
你是對的。
No, no, don't touch it!
不，不，不要去碰它！
What did I just tell you?
什么也我只是告訴你嗎？
I didn't touch anything!
我沒有碰任何東西！
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
對不起，對不起
Let's get out of here!
讓我們在這里了！
Go!
去！
Hurry, John!
快點，約翰！
Ok, come on.
好的，來吧。
Clip in.
夾在。
You in?
你呢？
- All set. - Ok.
- 所有設置。- 確定。
Remote.
遙控器。
Slack is out.
松弛超出。
Come on.
來吧。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
It's not working.
它不工作。
No.
沒有。
Give me yours, we'll go together.
給我你的，我們會一起去。
Clip in.
夾在。
Come on, come on!
來吧，來吧！
I'm sorry.
對不起。
What're you doing??
在那里，你在做什么？
Terry!
特里！
I'm sorry, brother.
對不起，哥哥。
We can do this together, come on!
我們能做到這一點起來，加油！
Terry, don't do this!
特里，不這樣做！
It's the only way.
這是唯一的辦法。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Terry!
特里！
I love you, man.
我愛你，男人。
Terry!!
特里！
My brother always stood by me
我哥哥總是陪伴著我。
even though he didn't always believe in
盡管他并不總是相信。
what I was doing.
我在做什么。
I guess that's what I'll miss most about him.
我想這就是我會最想念他的。
Luh...
LUH 。
I want to thank everybody for coming today
我要感謝大家的光臨今天。
and paying your respects.
和你付尊重。
It would mean a lot to my brother.
這將意味著很多我的兄弟。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Mommy, I miss my daddy.
媽媽，我想念我的爸爸。
I know you miss your daddy, sweetie.
我知道你想念你的爸爸，親愛的。
I miss your daddy, too.
我想念你的爸爸，太。
And if there's anything ever that you need,
如果有什么以往任何時候都需要，
you ask your Uncle John, ok?
你問你的叔叔約翰，好不好？
Ok, Uncle John.
好吧，叔叔約翰。
I guess it runs in the family.
我猜它運行在家庭。
What's that?
那是什么？
No body, no casket.
沒有身體，沒有棺材。
Laura, I'm so sorry.
勞拉，我很抱歉。
I...
我。
It wasn't your fault.
這不是你的錯。
He was my little brother.
他是我的小兄弟。
I should have protected him. He didn't have to come with me.
我應該保護他。他沒有跟我。
He looked up to you.
他抬頭看向你。
He would have followed you anywhere.
他會跟著你的任何地方。
- Professor Winston? - Not now, please.
- 溫斯頓教授？ - 不是現在，拜托。
- Hello, Professor Winston. - Ladies.
- 你好，教授溫斯頓。 - 女士。
Do you mind telling me what this is?
你介意告訴我這是什么？
What's it look like?
它像什么？
It looks like my classes have been cancelled.
它看起來像我的課被取消了。
That is what it says, yes.
這就是它說，是的。
Would you care to elucidate?
你會關心澄清？
I don't understand why.
我不明白為什么。
I thought after your brother's death
我想你的兄弟去世后。
you might want some time.
你可能需要一些時間。
Hmm.
嗯。
No, I don't need time.
不，我不需要時間。
I just need to get back to my teaching.
我只是需要找回我的教學。
It isn't quite that easy, John.
它不是想象中的那么容易，約翰。
You're the head of the department, Gerry.
你是部門負責人，格里。
Why don't you just make it that easy?
你為什么不只是讓那么容易嗎？
I'm the head of the department who must answer
我是誰必須回答的部門負責人。
to the president of the college,
該學院的院長，
who in turn has to answer to the board of trustees.
誰又將有回答董事會。
And what do the trustees have to do with any of this?
又哪里受托人必須做任何這樣？
You're the one who told these kids
你是誰告訴這些孩子之一。
about some god forsaken crystal skull story.
一些神離棄水晶頭骨的故事。
Gerald, are you kidding me now?
杰拉德，你現在跟我開玩笑吧？
It's just a theory.
它只是一個理論。
You and I both know that.
你和我都知道，。
That's right, a theory.
這是正確的，理論。
Isn't that what we're trying to do here?
這不正是我們試圖在這里做？
To help kids think for themselves?
幫助孩子為自己著想？
One of the school's largest donors objected.
學校最大的捐助者之一反對。
My hands are tied.
我的雙手被縛。
So now donors dictate curriculum?
所以現在的捐助者決定的課程？
They were going to pull the funding, John.
他們要拉資金，約翰。
All the funding.
所有的資金。
We're talking fifty faculty jobs.
我們談論50教師職位。
Ok, alright.
好吧，好吧。
Tell me who it is.
告訴我是誰。
I'll talk to them, maybe I can convince them, if-
我會告訴他們，也許我可以說服他們，如─
No, there's no convincing them.
沒有，有沒有說服他們。
Their minds are made up.
他們的想法是由。
You're a world class archaeologist, John,
你是一個世界級的考古學家約翰，
and a fine academic.
和罰款的學術。
You had to know that something like this
你必須知道，這樣的事情。
would catch up with you sooner or later.
會趕上你遲早。
John. I am truly sorry about this.
約翰。我真的很遺憾。
Me too.
我也是。
He's been in there a long time.
他一直在那里很長一段時間。
Give it a few more minutes.
給它一個幾分鐘。
A few more minutes and he'll have a bloody lap dance.
又過了幾分鐘，我們將有一個血淋淋的大腿舞。
Alright, that's it.
好吧，這就是它。
Leave it any longer and he's going to be absolutely smashed.
離開它的任何時間更長，他將絕對砸了。
Look on the bright side. You can carry him out.
看到光明的一面。你可以隨身攜帶他出去。
I'm not going to have him throw up on my brand new suit.
我不會讓他扔了我的新衣服。
Come on.
來吧。
If you've got a pen, I'll sign it for you.
如果你有一支筆，我就簽給你。
If you're lucky, some day it'll be worth something.
如果你是幸運的，哪天它會是值得的東西。
Actually, our employer is very interested
實際上，你的雇主非常感興趣。
in discussing it with you.
與您討論吧。
Alright,
好吧，
what is his or her name? I will make it out to he or she-
什么是他或她的名字？我會做出來給他 -
William Hadden.
威廉·哈登。
H-A-D-D-E-N.
H-A-D-D-E-N 。
William Hadden?
威廉·哈登？
The very wealthy technology fellow?
非常富有的技術家伙？
Yeah, that'd be the one.
是啊，這會是一個。
Now what would he want with my book?
現在什么，他想與我的書？
Not your book, mate.
不是你的書，隊友。
You.
你。
Me?
我呢？
Let's just say for the moment that he has a very deep,
讓我們只說對他有很深的那一刻，
personal interest in the subject matter.
個人興趣在題材。
Well, perhaps you should tell Mr. Hadden
好了，也許你應該告訴先生。哈登。
that he's slightly misguided.
他是稍微誤導。
Crystal skulls are a theory.
水晶頭骨是一個理論。
Apparently not a very good one.
顯然不是一個非常好的。
Oh s my'
哦，我的'。
Well, what if we told you
那么，如果我們告訴你。
it was a little more than just a theory.
這是一個有點不僅僅是一個理論。
I'd say that you guys need another drink.
我想說的是，你們需要再喝一杯。
And by "you guys" I mean me.
并通過你們我的意思是我。
Please.
請。
It's me.
這是我。
Yes, they are inside now.
是的，他們都在里面，現在。
I understand my mission.
我明白我的使命。
They will not acquire the thirteenth skull.
他們不會獲得第十三頭骨。
It sounds like you want me to make a statement.
這聽起來像你要我作出聲明。
Fine.
精。
It will be handled that way.
它將被處理這樣。
So I take it you don't want me to sign the book?
所以我想你不會要我簽書？
Mr. Hadden would like you to accompany us to Vienna.
先生。哈登愿意陪我們到維也納。
He would like to talk to you in person about the skulls.
他想和你談談本人對頭骨。
Vienna sounds lovely.
維也納聽起來可愛。
But unfortunately I've got some students,
但不幸的是我有一些同學，
lectures to attend to.
講座參加到。
Really?
真的嗎？
Because we heard you've been given a sabbatical
因為我們聽說你已經被賦予了休假。
from your teaching obligations.
從你的教學義務。
Oh, you heard about that?
哦，你聽說過嗎？
Mr. Hadden was the one that relieved you
先生。哈登是一個減輕你。
of those obligations.
這些義務。
Now why would he want to do that?
現在，他為什么還要那樣做？
He's got bigger fish to fry, no?
他有更大的魚魚苗，不是嗎？
He wants you to come to Vienna
他要你來維也納。
to discuss you and your father's life's work.
討論你和你父親的一生的工作。
He thought it would be better if he had your
他認為這將是更好，如果他有你的。
Get him out!
讓他出來！
Up the stairs! Go!!!!
上樓梯！去！
Who was that guy and why was he shooting at you?
誰是這家伙，為什么他在你拍攝的？
He wasn't shooting at me, he was aiming for you!
他沒有拍攝我，他瞄準了你！
He was what?
他是什么？
The thirteenth skull is still out there
第十三頭骨仍然在那里。
and there are people who would do anything to stop it
還有人誰愿意做任何事情來阻止它。
from being found.
從被發現。
Including fanatics like that guy.
包括像那家伙的狂熱分子。
Well if Hadden wanted my undivided attention,
那么，如果哈登希望我一心一意，
he certainly has it now.
他肯定現在有吧。
Go, go!
走，走！
I want updates on the Vienna pulse.
我想在維也納脈沖更新。
There's still an electro-magnetic signal
還是有電磁信號。
being generated from the location, sir.
從位置，先生正在生成。
What's the source?
什么是源？
No way to tell yet, sir.
沒有辦法告訴沒有，先生。
Signal strength is holding steady,
信號強度保持穩定，
no signs of dissipating.
散熱的跡象。
So they're still capable of generating another pulse?
所以他們仍然能夠產生另一個脈沖的？
Yes, colonel.
是的，上校。
If the second one is stronger,
如果第二個越強，
they could black out half of Europe.
他們可以歐洲黑掉一半。
Notify local authorities on the ground in Vienna.
在維也納地上通知地方當局。
And I want a go team assembled in 15 minutes on the pad.
我想組裝在15分鐘內上墊一個圍棋隊。
How much longer?
需要多少時間？
We land at Heathrow, and then we're going on a chopper
我們降落在希思羅機場，然后我們會在菜刀。
for the final leg to Vienna.
在最后一站到維也納。
A chopper?
菜刀？
I kinda like the jet.
我還挺喜歡的噴氣。
The EMP burst nearly dropped every plane from the sky
在EMP一陣幾乎降至每架飛機從天空。
around Vienna, so, for our own protection,
維也納左右，所以，為了我們自己的保護，
we're switching to a form of travel
我們切換到旅游的一種形式。
that's a little less precarious.
這是有點不太岌岌可危。
A little less precarious?
少岌岌可危？
Lower your weapons!
放下你的武器！
Put 'em down! Now!
把'時間了！現在！
Go to the left.
去左邊。
Move!
感動！
The rest of you men, on me.
你休息的人，對我。
That's far enough, Colonel.
這是遠遠不夠的，上校。
Order your men to lower their weapons.
命令你的手下，放下他們的武器。
You lower your weapons, sir.
放下你的武器，先生。
This is a private property and therefore
這是一種私有財產，因此。
you have no authority to enter this facility.
你無權進入該設施。
Really?
真的嗎？
I'm the United States Army commanding NATO forces.
我是美國陸軍指揮北約部隊。
I've got the authority to call in a damn air strike
我已經得到了權威的該死的空襲打電話。
on this building if I wanted to.
在這棟樓，如果我想。
You really want to go down that road?
你真的想要走這條道路？
You're out-gunned, son.
你洛迪克，兒子。
Tell your men to put their weapons down
告訴你的導師把他們的武器下來。
and no one gets hurt
沒有人會受到傷害。
Alright.
好吧。
So, who's in charge of this facility?
因此，誰負責這個設施的？
That would be me.
這將是我。
Colonel Bailey, I assume?
上校貝利，我承擔？
I'm afraid, sir,
我很害怕，先生，
that there's going to be a change of command.
有將是指令的變化。
This is a private research facility
這是一個私人研究機構。
wholly owned by Hadden Enterprises,
由哈登企業全資，
which is a private company wholly owned by me.
這是我所全資擁有的私人公司，。
What it is, Mr. Hadden,
它是什么，先生。哈登，
is the site of an unauthorized electro-magnetic pulse.
是未經授權的電磁脈沖的部位。
I'm authorized by NATO
我對北約授權。
to seize control of this wholly owned facility
抓住這一獨資設施的控制。
until I know what the hell is happening here.
直到我知道這到底是發生在這里。
I will be filing a formal complaint with the EU.
我將提出正式投訴與歐盟。
You do that, sir.
你這樣做，先生。
Until I hear otherwise, Mr. Hadden,
直到我聽到，否則，先生。哈登，
there's a new sheriff in town.
有一個在城里有一個新警長。
So this is the best a billionaire
所以這是最好的一個億萬富翁。
could come up with, huh?
能想出，是吧？
An old military-style helicopter?
一個古老的軍事風格的直升機？
They have far less electronics, which makes them safer to fly
它們具有少得多的電子，這使得它們更安全飛行。
when you have problems with EMP.
當你有問題，EMP 。
That's very comforting.
這是非常令人欣慰。
Sienna, I was wondering...
西耶娜，我想知道。
what's Hadden's obsession with the crystal skulls?
什么是霍頓的癡迷與水晶頭骨？
You need to ask him about that.
你要問他關于那個。
If I get a chance, I will.
如果我有機會，我會。
We have breaking news here.
我們已經分手的消息在這里。
It has just been confirmed that the electrical
它剛剛被證實，所述電。
disturbance that caused recent power outages
騷亂導致近停電。
across western Europe did in fact center
在西歐那樣，其實中心。
from Hadden Industries research facilities...
從哈登行業研究機構。
...As you may remember, the owner of Hadden Industries
。你可能還記得，哈登行業的老板。
is billionaire, William S. Hadden,
是億萬富翁，威廉二世。哈登，
a man who recently shocked Wall Street
一個人誰最近震驚華爾街。
when he decided to sell all of his US interests
當他決定賣掉他的所有美國利益的。
to pursue European projects...
追求歐洲項目。
...As you may recall, the Hadden facility is the same facility
。你可能還記得，隱藏的工具是一樣的設施。
associated with the EMP blast that blacked out
與EMP爆炸了涂黑有關。
most of western Europe.
大多數西歐。
We are awaiting an official statement and comments
我們正在等待一份官方聲明和評論。
from Hadden representatives,
從哈登的代表，
given the nature of the incident,
鑒于事件的性質，
on what exactly happened.
上究竟發生了什么。
What's going on?
這是怎么回事？
The magnetic field is growing.
磁場生長。
Faster than the last one?
比前一個更快？
Exponentially.
指數。
What the hell is this?
到底是什么呢？
There's nothing we can do to control the reaction.
還有，我們可以做些什么來控制反應沒有。
It's breaking away.
它打破。
Can someone please explain what I am looking at?
可有人請解釋什么，我在看什么？
These are twelve crystal skulls gathered from around the world,
這些來自世界各地聚集12水晶頭骨，
brought together for the first time.
匯集首次。
What in God's name are you talking about?
在神的名字是什么，你說什么？
I'm telling you that there's going to be another
我告訴你，那里將是另一個。
electro-magnetic pulse, larger than the first one.
電磁脈沖，比第1大。
Generated by these crystal skulls?
這些水晶頭骨產生的？
Yes.
是的。
And there isn't anything we can do to stop it.
并沒有什么我們可以做些什么來阻止它。
Well I'm going to stop it.
嗯，我要去停止它。
Weapons free, destroy the skulls.
武器自由，摧毀頭骨。
Colonel, no.
上校，沒有。
Colonel, please!
上校，拜托了！
You have no idea what you're doing!
你不知道你在做什么！
Fire!
火！
Ahhhhhhhhh!!!!!!!!
啊！ ！
What the hell was that?
這到底是什么？
Some kind of electronic pulse fried us.
某種電子脈沖油炸我們。
I thought that this old chopper was protected from that?
我認為，這個老菜刀保護呢？
Navigation systems have protection,
導航系統有保護，
but the fuel pumps were updated last year.
但燃油泵，去年進行了更新。
And you didn't think, that when we needed a chopper
你沒有想到，當我們需要一把菜刀。
with pre-sold electronics, that that might be an issue?
與預售電子，即可能是一個問題？
We've got no power?
我們有沒有權力？
We're in a helicopter.
我們在直升機。
We're going to fall like a stone from the sky.
我們將要墜落，像一塊石頭從天上。
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
We can auto-rotate.
我們可以自動旋轉。
Auto-what?
自動什么？
Choppers are just like planes.
菜刀就像飛機。
The blade on the top acts like a giant wing except
在上面的行為一樣，除了一個巨大的機翼的鋸片。
we've got to start diving to make this work,
我們必須開始跳水，使這項工作，
and this is a really bad place to auto-rotate and land.
這是一個非常糟糕的地方，自動旋轉和土地。
We'll need to re-route the power to the fuel pump.
我們需要重新路由的電源，燃油泵。
Well how the hell are we going to do that?!
以及如何地獄我們要做到這一點？ ！
Well, we can figure something out back there.
好了，我們可以想辦法回到那里。
You know how to do this?
你知道如何做到這一點？
We have to figure out where the fuel pump is.
我們要找出其中的燃油泵。
How long have we got until we have to put this thing down?
多久，我們得到了，直到我們必須把這個東西了嗎？
At this rate of descent, maybe another two minutes,
以這樣的速度的下降，也許另一個兩分鐘，
but we're going to have a hard landing
但我們將不得不硬著陸。
in the side of a mountain.
在山的一側。
I found a genie.
我發現了一個精靈。
Power cables.
電力電纜。
I found them right here.
我發現他們在這里。
Fuel pumps are up there.
燃油泵是在那里。
Put it into this up here, look.
把它放到這了這里，看。
These are the fuel lines here?
這些燃料線在這里？
Yeah.
是啊。
We're not going to clear the mountain range!
我們不會以清除山脈！
My job is to get these two people back,
我的工作是讓這兩個人回來，
we're not ditching!
我們不拋棄！
Got it?
得到它了？
We've got engine power back!
我們已經得到了發動機的動力又回來了！
Yes, nice!
是的，不錯！
That's awesome!
這是真棒！
Excellent work, professor, excellent!
出色的工作，教授，優秀的！
I think he's waking up.
我覺得他醒來。
Nice job, you save the poor bastard
不錯的工作，你救貧混蛋。
and we get the chopper up!
我們得到的菜刀起來！
Not too bad, if I say so myself!
差不太多，如果我這樣說我自己！
No, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不！
Oh, that's just brilliant, bloody brilliant!
哦，這只是輝煌，血腥的輝煌！
No gas!
無氣！
You loaded a generator with no fuel?
你不裝燃油發電機？
Sorry, sir.
對不起，先生。
Just shut up!
我閉嘴！
I need you--
我需要你-
I want to thank you for inviting me on this little adventure.
我要感謝你邀請我這個小小的冒險。
Professor--
Professor-
Move. move, move!!!!!
移動。動，動了！ ！
You alright?
你還好嗎？
That was a nice way to arrive in Europe.
這是一個很好的方式，在歐洲到達。
Yeah, you're welcome, Professor.
是啊，你別客氣，教授。
Now we've got to find transport to Vienna.
現在我們已經找到交通工具前往維也納。
What the hell just happened?
什么是地獄剛剛發生了什么？
You attempted to destroy them.
你試圖消滅他們。
There is no way to remove them or destroy them.
有沒有辦法將其刪除或銷毀。
Do you now understand that, Colonel?
你現在明白了，上校？
We're still online, Mr. Hadden.
我們仍然在線，先生。哈登。
Check redundant systems.
檢查冗余系統。
Sir,
先生，
I'm receiving a signal from the helicopter
我是從直升機上接收信號。
transporting doctors Mallory and Winston.
運送醫生馬洛里和溫斯頓。
What kind of signal?
什么樣的信號？
An emergency beacon.
緊急燈塔。
The chopper is down.
菜刀下跌。
Are there any casualties?
是否有任何傷亡？
Any injuries?
任何傷害？
Don't know, sir.
不知道，先生。
Dammit!
該死！
They must have flown right through the pulse.
他們一定的權利，通過脈沖飛行。
Get a location on the crash site.
坐上了失事地點的位置。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
Who was on this chopper?
誰是這個菜刀？
Sienna Mallory, my senior researcher,
西耶娜·馬洛里，我的高級研究員，
and John Winston.
和約翰·溫斯頓。
Winston? Professor John Winston?
溫斯頓？教授約翰·溫斯頓？
Yes, Colonel.
是的，上校。
He might just be the only one who can stop this.
他可能只是誰也阻止不了這個唯一一個。
But presently my only concern
但目前我只關注。
is for Miss Mallory's well-being.
是懷念馬洛里的幸福。
I just lost four soldiers, Mr. Hadden.
我只是失去了四名士兵，先生。哈登。
I'm not particularly concerned with your personal decadences.
我不是特別關心你的個人decadences 。
Sienna Mallory is my daughter, Colonel.
西耶娜·馬洛里是我的女兒，上校。
So please,
所以請，
use whatever resources you have at your disposal
使用你有什么資源，在您的處置。
and get them here as soon as possible.
并讓他們在這里盡快。
Give my men those coordinates and I'll send a recovery team.
給我的男人的坐標，我會送回收隊伍。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
Mr. Hadden, I'm sorry.
先生。哈登，對不起。
I'm a father as well.
我是一個父親，以及。
Thank you, Colonel.
謝謝你，上校。
Apology accepted.
道歉接受。
Colonel! You have to see this!
上校！你必須看到這個！
I've just arrived here in Berlin where members of the G8
我剛在柏林的地方八國集團成員。
are now gathering for what seems to be an emergency meeting
現在收集了什么似乎是一個緊急會議。
regarding these strange weather phenomena
對于這些奇怪的天氣現象。
which seem to be increasing by the hour.
這似乎增加了每小時。
This weather phenomena has now reached critical mass
這樣的天氣phenomenahas現在已經達到臨界質量。
as you can see, it's now become a massive vortex!
你可以看到，它現在已經成為一個巨大的漩渦！
I've just received breaking news that the military units
我剛剛收到突發新聞，軍事單位。
have now been moved into the city to assist with evacuation.
現在已經轉移到城市，以協助疏散。
Now reports say
現在報道說。
that a lightening storm has tripled in size
一個閃電風暴兩倍大小。
over the last 24 hours,
在過去的24小時，
and that the giant vortex is now engulfing the city.
和巨旋渦現在席卷全市。
But as the vortex drifts farther across Europe,
但隨著旋渦越飄過歐洲，
I think the question on everybody's lips is
我認為每個人的嘴唇問題是。
where do we evacuate to?
我們在哪里避難？
What is this?
這是什么？
If I'm right, it's the beginning of the end.
如果我是對的，這是結束的開始。
Don't take this the wrong way,
不要采取這種錯誤的方式，
but I hope to God you're wrong.
但我希望上帝你錯了。
Mr. Hadden, we have no choice.
先生。哈登，我們別無選擇。
We have to contain the lab and destroy the skulls.
我們必須遏制實驗室和破壞頭骨。
That is impossible, Colonel.
那是不可能的，上校。
We can't just sit here and do nothing!
我們不能坐在這里什么都不做！
Daddy!
爸爸！
I thought I had lost you!
我以為我已經失去了你！
Professor John Winston,
教授約翰·溫斯頓，
I'd like you to meet William Hadden.
我想你見見威廉·哈登。
My father.
我的父親。
Mr. Hadden.
先生。哈登。
Professor, I was a great admirer of your father's,
教授，我是你的父親是一個偉大的崇拜者，
as I am of you yourself.
因為我是你自己。
This is Colonel Bailey.
這是上校貝利。
Bailey.
貝利。
Professor.
教授。
I appreciate the kind words,
我很欣賞的客氣話，
I don't meet many fans of my father's
我不符合我的父親很多球迷。
except for fringe groups and lunatics.
除了邊緣群體和狂人。
Well, I hope I'm neither.
好了，我希望我沒有。
Before I lost my ability to walk,
之前，我失去了我的腿腳，
it was where I did my best thinking.
這是在那里我做了我最好的思想。
So, if you don't mind, shall we walk together?
所以，如果你不介意的話，我們應該一起走？
I don't mind at all, if you don't mind explaining to me
我不介意，如果你不介意的話解釋給我。
what exactly it is that I'm doing here.
它究竟是什么，我在這里做。
I'm a very wealthy man, Doctor Winston.
我是一個非常富有的人，醫生溫斯頓。
I have been for most of my life.
我一直在為我一生中最。
But, I fear my hubris has gotten the better of me
但是，我擔心我的傲慢已經得到了我的好。
in the light of what is now happening.
在目前所發生的事情光。
I'll put this as simply as I can.
我會把它作為簡單的，我可以。
You're here, Doctor Winston, because I am dying.
你在這里，醫生溫斯頓，因為我快死。
I have been fighting cancer for ten years.
我一直在與癌癥作斗爭了十年。
In my pursuit of a cure,
在我的追求治愈的，
I became aware of the crystal skulls
我才知道水晶頭骨。
and began to acquire them.
并開始收購這些。
All of them but the thirteenth.
所有的人，但第十三。
Yes.
是的。
The first were found in South America,
第一個被發現在南美洲，
followed by three others-
接著是三個其他 -
Forgive me for interrupting, sir,
原諒我打斷了，先生，
I understand the history
據我所知，歷史上。
but all the skulls have proven to be a fraud,
但所有的頭骨已被證明是一個欺詐，
carbon dating has tested them to be no older
碳定年測試了他們沒有老。
than 200 or 300 years.
超過200或300年。
Trust me, we have had our failures.
相信我，我們有我們的失敗。
No one's perfect.
沒有一個完美的。
Let's just say the tests were somewhat suspect.
讓我們只說測試是有些犯罪嫌疑人。
Suspect?
懷疑？
What are you saying?
你在說什么？
The carbon dating was altered somehow?
碳定年是改變以某種方式？
You got the twelve different skulls
你得到了十二種不同的頭骨。
from all different pans of the world?
來自世界各個不同地區？
Hadden Industries owns
哈登行業擁有。
six of the largest carbon dating facilities.
六個最大的碳年代測定設施。
So the tests were fake?
所以測試是假的？
Let's just say we have a higher standard of proof.
讓我們只說我們有證據更高的標準。
Ah, right, right.
啊，對吧。
You duped the whole scientific community.
你欺騙了整個科學界。
What we did was soften the purchase price
我們所做的是softenthe收購價格。
to take them off the museum displays.
把他們趕走館內陳列。
Mr. Hadden may be a billionaire,
先生。哈登可以成為億萬富翁，
but everyone has their price.
但每個人都有自己的價格。
Right, right.
右，右。
So it's about money.
所以它的錢。
We're talking about putting together
我們談論放在一起。
twelve of the most precious objects in the world.
12世界上最珍貴的對象。
Something that would not happen if the truth
什么，如果真不會發生。
became common knowledge.
成為眾矢之的。
Mr. Hadden, I don't know what the implications are
先生。哈登，我不知道是什么含義是。
of you altering these tests,
你改變這些試驗中，
but I imagine it involves prison.
但我想它涉及監獄。
I am dying, Colonel.
我要死了，上校。
Yeah, well, you're not dead yet.
是啊，好了，你還沒死。
Ok, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Ok了，堅持住，堅持住，堅持。
None of this really matters now.
沒有這個，現在真正重要的。
The skulls are real.
頭骨是真實的。
So how old are they?
所以他們多大？
Most of them were dated about 500,000 years ago.
他們大多是過時大約50萬年前。
Others cannot be dated.
別人無法日期。
500,000 years?
50萬年？
That pre-dates man.
那人早。
Which implies some other origin.
這意味著一些其他來源。
Perhaps extraterrestrials?
也許是外星人？
Mr. Hadden, I don't know if your carbon dating shenanigans
先生。哈登，我不知道，如果你的碳約會有心計。
have lead to this disaster,
已導致這場災難，
but I do know that I have another problem.
但我知道，我還有一個問題。
Preventing the end of the world.
防止全球的端。
You and I have the same goal, Colonel.
你和我有同樣的目標，上校。
Colonel!
上校！
Enough!
夠了！
Now if you and Professor Winston can come up with a solution,
現在，如果你和教授溫斯頓能拿出一個解決方案，
I'm all ears.
我所有的耳朵。
But now I must confer with NATO
但現在我必須賦予北約。
and come up with our own method.
并拿出我們自己的方法。
Brute force will not work!
蠻力將無法正常工作！
You saw what happened when your men attempted
你所看到的happenedwhen你的人試圖。
to attack the skulls!
攻擊的頭骨！
They have an impregnable field around them!
他們有一個堅不可摧的領域身邊！
That was four men.
那是四個人。
I'm talking about some stronger medicine.
我說的是一些藥更強。
We know force won't work.
我們知道強行將不起作用。
What Will?
會是怎樣？
The thirteenth skull.
第十三頭骨。
But the dilemma is
但困境是。
I have no idea where to begin to look for it.
我不知道從哪里開始尋找它。
I want you to follow your father's footsteps
我想你跟著你父親的腳步。
and find it.
并發現它。
Fulfill your destiny.
滿足你的命運。
Mr. Hadden-
先生。 hadden-
Every single one of my resources
我的資源，每一個人。
will be at your disposal.
將在您的處置。
God knows I created this disaster.
上帝知道我創造了這個災難。
If I have to use every bit of my fortune to stop it,
如果非要用我的財富每一位來阻止它，
so be it.
這樣吧。
There's one thing that neither one of us has much of.
有一件事，我們沒有一個有很大的。
And what would that be?
而那會是什么？
Time.
時間。
So am I to assume this chopper is safer than the last one?
所以我該承擔這個菜刀是比上一個更安全？
It's Cold War technology.
這是冷戰技術。
It's built to withstand a nuclear explosion.
它的建成能夠承受核爆炸。
So why didn't you tell me that Hadden was your father?
所以你為什么不告訴我，哈登是你的父親嗎？
And spoil the surprise?
和破壞的驚喜呢？
You know, we have a lot in common, Professor.
你知道，我們有很多共同點，教授。
Really?
真的嗎？
What's that?
那是什么？
We've both spent our lives trying to get out of the shadow
我們倆度過了我們的生活努力走出陰影。
of our fathers.
我們的父輩。
Is that what Mallory is?
是什么馬洛里是？
It was my mother's maiden name.
這是我母親的娘家姓。
She died when I was a little girl.
她去世時，我是一個小女孩。
Would it have made a difference if you had known who I was?
將它作出了區別，如果你已經知道我是誰嗎？
In what, how seriously I took you?
什么，我多么認真了嗎？
Or how attractive I thought you were when we first met?
或者多么誘人我還以為你是當我們第一次見面？
Seriously?
認真？
So, do you uh...
所以，你呃。
always wait until you get a girl alone in a helicopter
一直等到你的直升機拿到一個女孩獨自。
before you bust a line like that out?
您胸圍之前這樣的行了呢？
No, I usually wait to find out if the girl I'm hitting on
不，我通常等待，看看是否這個女孩我打的。
is the daughter of the billionaire.
是億萬富翁的女兒。
Oh, sure.
哦，肯定。
Well then I guess it's a shame
那么我想這是一個恥辱。
that my inheritance is being held in a living trust.
我繼承被關押在生前信托。
Ahh.
啊。
So where are we going?
所以我們要去哪里？
Your father told me to follow in my father's footsteps.
你爸爸告訴我，在我父親的后塵。
That is what I'm doing.
這就是我在做什么。
The thirteenth skull is down there?
第十三頭骨是在哪兒？
No, this is the last place my father came
不，這是我的父親來到了最后的地方。
before he disappeared.
他消失前。
And this is the only way down?
這是唯一的辦法了嗎？
I'm afraid so.
恐怕是。
Ready?
準備好了嗎？
We're here.
我們在這里。
Easy, easy.
方便，易于。
I've got ya.
我得雅。
That's interesting.
這是有趣的。
What?
什么？
Since I was here with Terry,
因為我在這里與特里，
I find that this cave has collapsed.
我發現這個洞穴已經崩潰。
That's good?
非常好？
Not if we need another way out.
不，如果我們需要另一條出路。
Or we could have avoided this entire extreme sports routine.
或者我們可能避免這整個極限運動例行。
Yeah, fat chance. Come on.
是的，脂肪的機會。來吧。
How did you get your father's notebook
你是怎么得到你父親的筆記本電腦。
if they never found his body?
如果他們從來沒有發現自己的身體？
It was sent to me at a college where I was teaching
這是送給我在一所大學在那里我教。
before your father had me fired.
你的父親在我面前解雇。
Ok, well that doesn't explain who sent it to you.
OK，很好，沒有解釋是誰發送給你。
You don't know?
你不知道？
It was your father.
這是你的父親。
He sent a note along with it.
他送出一記隨之。
He said that one of his researchers had found it
他說，他的研究人員的一個發現它。
on an expedition and he thought perhaps one day
遠征，他覺得或許有一天。
I would find it useful.
我會覺得有用。
So this was the last place your father was?
所以這是最后的地方你的父親是？
This is where they found the notebook?
這是在那里他們發現了筆記本電腦？
I'd be inclined to agree with you.
我傾向于同意你的。
But if my father's research team had already been here
但如果我父親的研究小組已經在這里了。
and they didn't find the thirteenth skull,
他們沒有找到第十三頭骨，
why are we here?
我們為什么在這里？
Hold this, please.
持此，請。
This is the last place that my father came.
這是我的父親來到了最后的地方。
Where my brother lost his life.
在我的弟弟失去了他的生活。
And I'm betting that the answer is still here.
和我打賭，答案還在這里。
We just have to know where to look for it.
我們只需要知道去哪里找吧。
Excuse me, gentlemen.
對不起，先生們。
What is it?
它是什么？
The skulls are generating a very focused magnetic field
頭骨都產生了非常集中的磁場。
which begins in the isolation chamber
它開始于隔離腔。
and extends out beyond the common line.
并伸出超出公用線。
That's the line that separates the Earth's atmosphere
這是分隔地球大氣層行。
from outer space.
來自外太空。
I know what it is.
我知道它是什么。
It seems that it now extends back to the Earth's core.
似乎現在向后延伸到地球的核心。
What the hell does all that mean, Mr. Hadden?
什么是地獄做所有的意思是，先生。哈登？
It means that there's now a new field
這意味著，現在有一個新的領域。
competing with the existing one.
與現有的1競爭。
Alright, so now give me the bad news.
好了，所以現在給我一個壞消息。
Volcanic and seismic activity,
火山與地震活動，
and a good possibility that the Earth's iron crust
和良好的可能性，即地球的地殼鐵。
will crack like an egg,
會開裂就像一個雞蛋，
and if that happens the planet will be literally torn apart
如果這種情況發生全球將有字面上撕裂。
And the good news?
而好消息嗎？
Mr. Pritchard.
先生。普里查德。
At the current rate, sir, roughly 30 hours.
以目前的速度，SAR，大約30小時。
- Issue an evacuation order. - Yes, sir.
- 發出疏散令。 - 是的，先生。
In 30 hours,
在30小時，
I am authorizing the use of a tactical
我授權使用的戰術。
nuclear weapon at this site.
核武器在這個網站。
I'll vaporize those god forsaken things
我會汽化那些神拋棄的東西。
back to wherever it is that they came from.
回到地方是，他們從來到。
You saw what happened when your men attempted
你所看到的所發生的當你的人試圖。
to destroy them!
消滅他們！
That was four soldiers, Mr. Hadden.
這是四名士兵，先生。哈登。
I'm talking about power that hasn't been unleashed
我說的是力量尚未釋放。
since Hiroshima.
自廣島。
You are going to be the man who ended the world.
你要成為結束世界的男人。
Or maybe saved it.
也許它保存。
You alright?
你還好嗎？
Mmmhmm.
嗯
This way.
這邊。
Good job.
做好。
- You ok? - Yeah.
- 你還好嗎？ - 是啊。
John?
約翰？
Look.
看。
John, you ok?
約翰，你還好嗎？
Yeah.
是啊。
Yeah, I'm fine.
是啊，我很好。
This is for you, my brother.
這是給你的，我的兄弟。
We're ready for the extraction.
我們已經準備好提取。
Go ahead
繼續。
Come on!
來吧！
We've gotta get out of this place!
我們得離開這個地方！
Yeah, no kidding.
是的，沒有開玩笑。
Come on.
來吧。
I'm glad that's behind us.
我很高興，這是我們后面。
We don't need these anymore.
我們不需要這些了。
Ok.
好。
Here, let me help you.
這里，讓我幫你。
Alright, this way.
好了，這邊。
Let's go, come on.
我們走 ，來吧。
What happened to the helicopter?
直升機怎么了？
Someone shot it down.
有人拍下來。
Who?
誰？
I don't know.
我不知道。
Probably the same person who shot at me in the bar.
大概誰開槍我在酒吧同一個人。
They stepped it up a notch or two.
他們加強它一個或兩個檔次。
Careful.
仔細。
Agh!
啊！
What're you doing? That really hurt!
你在干什么？那真痛啊！
Mitchell, what the hell are you doing here?
米切爾，你到底在這做什么？
Oh now come on.
哦，現在來吧。
You didn't really think Mr. Hadden
你真的沒有想到先生。哈登。
was going to let you traipse halfway across Europe
打算讓你在歐洲中途拖曳。
with his precious little girl
他珍愛的小女孩。
with nobody to keep an eye on you, did you?
有沒有人讓你的眼睛，是不是？
What happened to the helicopter?
直升機怎么了？
Someone took it down with a missile.
有人用導彈把它打下來了。
Someone who seems to be intent on killing me.
有人似乎有意殺害我。
Do you have any idea who?
你能想到誰？
Religious fanatics, fringe groups,
宗教狂熱分子，邊緣群體，
- white supremacists, CIA... - Alright, alright.
- 白人至上主義者，中央情報局。 - 好吧，好吧。
You know, all I know is that before I met you
你知道，我所知道的是，在我遇見你。
I had no idea that anyone would want to kill me.
我不知道，怎么會有人想要殺我。
I'm a likable enough kind of guy.
我是一個十分討人喜歡的那種人。
So you say. Now look,
所以你說。你聽著，
do you want to stand around here and talk about
你想站在這兒，談談。
the assassins who are after you,
誰是在你的刺客，
or do you want to get the hell out of here
或者你想獲得地獄離開這里。
before they work out that you weren't in the chopper
他們的工作之前，你是不是在菜刀。
that they shot down?
他們擊落？
Yeah, that's what I thought.
是啊，這就是我想。
I want an EMP-shielded chopper standing by
我想要一個EMP-屏蔽銅纜站在。
to pull the rest of us out of here when the time comes.
拉我們其余的人離開這里到時候。
Yes, sir.
是的，長官。
They'll be here.
他們將在這里。
I hope you're right.
我希望你是對的。
For everyone's sake.
每個人的緣故。
Because I don't want to go down in history
因為我不想名垂青史。
as the man who authorized the detonation of a nuclear device
因為誰授權的核裝置的引爆的人。
to save the world.
拯救世界。
Then don't do it, Colonel.
那就不要做了，上校。
It's out of my hands.
這是從我手中。
We should put these lights out and kill that heater.
我們應該把這些燈出來，并殺死加熱器。
It could attract the wrong kind of company,
它會吸引了錯誤樣的公司，
if you know what I mean.
如果你知道我的意思。
Yeah, well I'm cold, and we need light to figure this out.
是啊，我冷，我們需要光算出這個。
Well, then you might as well send up a signal flare
好，那你還不如送了一個信號彈。
and tell whoever is after us where we are.
并告訴誰是我們后，我們都。
Maybe you should put out that cheap cigar you're smoking.
也許你應該拿出你吸煙，廉價雪茄。
The smell will attract the wrong kind of people.
氣味會吸引了錯誤的那種人。
It's a Cohiba.
這是一個科伊巴。
Oh, well perfect.
哦，還有完善的。
In that case we'll only attract
在這種情況下，我會只吸引了。
the best kind of terrorists and assassins.
最好的一種恐怖分子和刺客。
Besides, that's why we have you here.
此外，這就是為什么我們有你在這里。
To protect us.
保護我們。
Yeah, well I can't protect you from yourselves.
是啊，我不能保護你自己。
It's not here.
它不是在這里。
It has to be.
它必須是。
Yeah, well I can't see it and I'm tired.
是啊，我還看不出來，我累了。
Maybe we should grab a couple of hours of sleep.
也許我們應該抓住幾個睡眠時間。
Start fresh.
重新開始。
The sun will be up soon.
太陽將高達很快。
Although, if we don't crack this it won't matter.
但是，如果我們不破解這個也沒什么關系。
How are we gonna get out of here without a chopper, Mitchell?
如何我們該怎么離開這里沒有菜刀，米切爾？
I'm not putting another bird up in the area
我不會把另外一只小鳥在該地區。
until we've secured it.
直到我們確保它。
Now listen, professor.
現在聽，教授。
You need to concentrate on saving the world.
你需要專注于拯救世界。
I need to get some fresh air so I can think.
我需要散散心，所以我能思考。
Go and give him a hand.
去給他一只手。
You see it?
你看到了嗎？
See what?
看什么？
There.
有。
There it is!
有啊！
I knew I would find it.
我知道我會找到它。
Let me show you where it is.
讓我告訴你它在哪里。
Have you two figured it out?
有你們兩個想通了？
Yeah, maybe.
是的，也許。
I need to report to Mr. Hadden and the Colonel
我需要報告的時間。哈登和上校。
if you've cracked this or not.
如果你已經破解這個還是不。
This is not the map, this is the place.
這不是地圖，這是地方。
These, these are the map.
這些，這些是地圖。
I'm not following you.
我不跟著你。
They're stars.
他們是明星。
This drawing shows us exactly where to find
此圖顯示的確切位置找到。
the thirteenth skull.
第十三頭骨。
I thought you'd be excited.
我還以為你會興奮。
Well, the temple in that cave must be 3000 years old.
好了，在洞穴寺廟必須是3000多年的歷史。
I'd say more like five.
我說更像是5 。
Oh, even better.
哦，甚至更好的。
So all we have to do is figure out
所以我們要做的就是想通了。
where that constellation appeared
其中，該星座出現。
in the night sky 5000 years ago?
在夜空中在5000年前？
Well, that's easy.
嗯，這很容易。
You know, I realize that in order for the two of us
你知道，我知道，為了讓我們兩個。
to figure it out it would take months, maybe longer.
弄明白這將需要數月，甚至更長的時間。
But for one of your dad's super computers
但對于你爸的超級計算機之一。
it should be a piece of cake.
它應該是小菜一碟。
Right.
正確的。
Alright,
好吧，
enter the declination and extrapolate.
輸入偏角和推斷。
Oh wait, we've got something.
哦，等等，我們已經得到的東西。
You two are a piece of work.
你們兩個是作品。
Right, you wanted to know where that constellation appeared
對了，你想知道的星座出現。
in the night sky 5000 years ago?
在夜空中在5000年前？
Well, actually 5302 months and 11 days.
嗯，其實5302個月11天。
There's your answer.
有你的答案。
What the hell is that?
這到底是什么？
It's the Visoko Valley, it's theoretically a pyramid.
它的維索科山谷，這是理論上的一個金字塔。
That's where we're going.
這是我們要去的地方。
太陽金字塔
It's interesting how it has remained unexplored
有趣的是它如何保持未開發。
for thousands of years.
千百年來。
People thought it was a natural formation for a long time.
人們認為這是一個自然形成的很長一段時間。
Oh, my father said the military put a clock on us.
哦，我的父親說，軍方把時鐘上我們。
We have six hours.
我們有六個小時。
I hope Mitchell gets back before the world ends
我希望米切爾世界末日前回來。
and he's out trying to rent a car.
和他出去想租一輛車。
Really?
真的嗎？
That's an interesting choice.
這是一個有趣的選擇。
That's our man, that's our man!
這是我們的人，這是我們的人！
Oh boy.
哦男孩。
You work for the wealthiest man in the world
你為世界上最富有的人工作。
and the best car you could rent was this?
竟然租到最好的車是這樣的？
Well, excuse me, Mr. Trump, but they didn't take credit cards
好了，對不起，王牌先生，但他們沒有用信用卡。
and this was all I could get with the cash I had.
這是所有我能得到的現金，我不得不。
Well, so where are we going?
好了，讓我們去哪兒？
Is that it?
是這樣嗎？
What were you expecting, Mitchell? Giza?
你到底在期待，米切爾？吉薩？
Well, I don't know, maybe something bigger than that?
好了，我不知道，也許更大的東西比？
It just looks like an odd-shaped hill.
它只是看起來像一個奇怪形狀的小山。
Well, it is a pyramid.
好了，這是一個金字塔。
Yeah, well I know that, Professor Smarty-Pants.
是啊，我知道，教授Smarty的褲。
All I'm saying is it doesn't look like a place
我要說它看起來并不像一個地方。
that would hold the key to save the world.
將持有的關鍵，拯救世界。
I see.
我看到。
And what do you suppose that would look like?
你期望什么樣子？
Ok, alright, so what's the plan?
好了，好了，所以有什么計劃？
We're gonna keep a low profile,
我們要保持低調，
stay away from the village until it gets dark,
遠離村莊，直到天黑，
and then go in nice and quiet.
然后去好和安靜。
That plan sounds as strong as the choice in cars.
這個計劃聽起來強如在汽車的選擇。
Get in the car.
坐進車內。
My goodness, could this be smaller?
我的天啊，還能再小嗎？
Where is everyone?
哪里是每個人？
How should I know?
我怎么會知道？
A town meeting, strip club?
一個鎮民大會，脫衣舞俱樂部？
Strip club?
脫衣舞俱樂部？
These are nice people.
這些都是很好的人。
You never know.
你永遠不知道。
Villages all need a good strip club.
村莊都需要一個良好的脫衣舞俱樂部。
A little early, wouldn't you say?
你不早說？
Well, I guess we know where everyone is.
好吧，我想我們都知道，每個人都。
We've got to get out.
我們得出去。
- This will pass, give it time. - Look behind you.
- 這會過去，給它時間。 - 看看你身后。
Oh, shoot.
哦，拍。
Get out.
出去。
Just act normal.
只是充當普通。
Don't look around.
不要東張西望。
Don't react.
還沒有反應過來。
Don't make it known we're being followed.
不要讓他們知道我們被跟蹤。
But we are being followed, so how are we supposed to act?
但我們被跟蹤，所以我們怎么行動？
Casual.
休閑。
How many are there?
究竟有多少？
There's two behind us and two in front of us.
還有我們兩個的后面，兩個在我們面前。
Just turn around and mingle.
剛轉身打成一片。
QKEY
好的
What are they doing?
他們在做什么？
I've seen you before.
我以前見過你。
Yes.
是的。
And I have seen you, as well.
我也見過你。
Now, I'm afraid this will be our last meeting.
現在，恐怕這將是我們最后一次見面。
Is that some kind of euphemism because you're going to kill us?
是，一些委婉的說法，因為你要殺死我們？
Easy, Sienna.
放松，西耶娜。
Don't antagonize the man.
不對抗的人。
He's got a sword.
他有一把劍。
Yeah, the professor has a point.
是的，這位教授有一個點。
Go on, enjoy your banter, because it will all end now.
去，享受你的玩笑，因為它會現在都結束。
What is it that you're after?
它是什么，你呢？
You know what we're after.
你知道我們是后。
You've been following us.
你一直跟著我們。
Yes.
是的。
It is ourjob to protect the thirteen.
這是我們的工作，保護第13個。
Skulls.
頭骨。
They possess incredible power when they are brought together.
他們擁有不可思議的力量，當他們匯聚。
Something your father did.
一些你父親做了。
Before you die, I wanted to ask you
你死之前，我想問問你。
what it is you thought would happen once you found that
你一旦發現你以為會發生什么。
which you seek?
你求？
We need to work together in order to stop it.
我們需要它阻止
Stop what?
阻止什么？
Don't you know?
你不知道嗎？
The destruction caused by the twelve skulls
12頭骨所造成的破壞。
being brought together.
正在匯聚。
We need the thifleenth to stop it.
我們需要第十三阻止它。
Well, if a man was foolish enough to trifle
還有，如果一個人是愚蠢的，對這種力量。
with this power,
視如兒戲，
then it is he who has brought upon himself this destruction.
那么他會自我毀滅。
You cannot save them.
你不能拯救他們。
Now prepare.
現在準備。
John!
約翰！
Don't worry, look away.
不用擔心，看開點。
It'll only take a second.
它只會花一秒鐘。
Stop!
住手！
Give me the sword.
給我的劍。
Hello, junior.
你好，朱莉亞。
Dad?
爸爸？
We buried you.
我們埋葬了你。
We thought you were dead somewhere.
我們以為你死了。
I'm sorry, son.
對不起，兒子。
We looked for you for so long, Dad.
我們找了你這么久，爸爸。
And then I found your journal.
然后我發現你的日記。
I left it in a place I knew it would be discovered.
我把它在一個地方，我知道它會被發現。
I had hoped if you found it, it would give you some answers.
我曾希望，如果你發現了它，它會給你一些答案。
It gave me answers, but far more questions.
它給了我答案，但目前更多的問題。
It's basically what got me here.
它基本上是什么讓我在這里。
What happened, Dad?
發生了什么事，爸爸？
Where did you go?
你去哪兒？
I know you have a lot of questions,
我知道你有很多的問題，
and you should.
你應該。
I've been after the thirteenth skull for so many years,
我一直在第十三后頭骨了這么多年，
I had come so close,
我來了這么近，
and then I found this place and the brotherhood.
然后我發現這個地方和兄弟會。
This is the brotherhood's last stronghold.
這是兄弟會的最后一個據點。
It holds the last of our secrets.
它守住我們最后的秘密。
What secrets?
什么樣的秘密？
I found the skull, John.
我發現頭骨，約翰。
It's real, just like I always knew it would be!
它是真實的，就像我一直都知道這將是！
They gave me a choice.
他們給了我一個選擇。
I could die,
我可以死，
or I could join with them
或者我可以加入與他們。
in protecting the secrets of the skulls.
在保護頭骨的秘密。
I had been searching so long, nothing else mattered.
我已經尋找了這么久，什么也不在乎。
Obviously your family didn't matter.
顯然你不在乎你的家人。
Your choice lead to your son's death.
你的選擇導致你兒子死亡。
Terry died wanting to follow in your footsteps.
泰利步你的后塵。
I loved you and your brother more than you will ever know,
我愛你和你的兄弟比你永遠不會知道，
but this was something I couldn't refuse.
但是這是我無法拒絕的。
After everything I had seen, everything I had learned.
一切后，我看到了，一切我已經學會了。
It wasn't a choice, it was my destiny.
這是不是一種選擇，這是我的命運。
Maybe your destiny could be put to good use.
也許你的命運，可以善加利用。
The world is the thirteenth skull, Dad.
世界第十三頭骨，爸爸。
You know they will never let you have it.
你知道他們永遠不會讓你擁有它。
Don't let Terry's death be in vain!
不要讓泰利無謂的犧牲！
Without the skull, billions will die.
沒有頭骨，數十億就會死亡。
If the skulls have been gathered,
如果頭骨已聚集，
and the end of the world has begun, so be it.
和世界末日已經開始，就這樣吧。
This is man's destiny.
這是人的命運。
Man's destiny rides on your shoulders.
人類的命運騎在你的肩膀。
You understand that they cannot ever leave this place now.
你明白，他們不能永遠離開這個地方，現在。
Yes, I know.
是的，我知道。
I only ask that I do not have to watch.
我只要求沒有看。
Yeah, we wouldn't want you to be upset
是的，我們不希望你心煩。
watching your last son be killed for your destiny!
看你最后一個兒子被殺害你的命運！
You're going to kill us here, in the pyramid?
你會殺了我們這里，在金字塔？
Do you have no honour?
你有沒有榮譽？
Woman, do not speak to me like this!
女人，不跟我說話這個樣子！
I have spent my life defending the honour of this place.
我已經花了我的一生捍衛榮譽這個地方。
There is never honour for those who kill, Hussein!
從未有紀念那些誰殺了，侯賽因！
I'm sorry, old friend.
對不起，老朋友。
Follow me, this way!
跟著我，這邊！
No, sir, the squadron is in the air awaiting orders.
沒有，先生，該中隊在空中待命。
The magnetic field is at 95 percent, sir.
磁場是95％，先生。
It's time we get everybody out of here.
這一次，我們讓所有人都離開這里。
Colonel, your bombs aren't going to do what you think they will.
上校，你的炸彈不會丟你認為他們會。
Just give them more time.
只要給他們更多的時間。
I'll give them as much time as I can.
我給他們盡可能多的時間。
After that, I'm under orders.
在那之后，我下命令。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Thank me if we all live that long.
如果我們每個人都生活那么久再感謝我。
We've gotta get out of here.
我們得離開這里。
Mitchell, call my father.
米切爾，叫上我爸爸。
Dad, what are you doing?
爸爸，你在做什么？
This place is my life, John.
這個地方是我的生命，約翰。
I have nowhere to go.
我無處可去。
Let me die here.
讓我死在這里。
I don't deserve to live after what I did to the brotherhood.
對兄弟會所做的我不值得活。
What're you talking about?!
你在說什么？
You have a different life now,
現在你有不同的生活，
you've got a granddaughter!
你已經有了一個孫女！
I have a granddaughter?
我有一個孫女？
Yes! Terry's daughter! She's going to be seven!
沒錯！泰利的女兒！她馬上7歲了！
Really? Yes!
真的嗎？ 是的！
Dad!
爸爸！
I'm sorry, son.
對不起，兒子。
Dad, no!
爸爸，不！
Come on, we have to go.
來吧，我們必須去。
John, come on! Now!
約翰，加油！現在！
- Dad! - Come on, John, now!
- 爸爸！ - 來吧，約翰，現在！
Sir, the magnetic fields are at 100 percent.
主席先生，磁場達到100％。
I'm afraid your people are out of time, Mr. Hadden.
我怕你的人都出來的時候，先生。哈登。
Alpha Squadron, time to target?
阿爾法中隊，時間目標？
Copy that.
復制。
Eight minutes.
8分鐘。
We've got to get everyone out at a safe minimum distance
我們必須讓每個人都出在一個安全的最小距離。
before detonation.
前引爆。
You heard them, they're on their way!
你聽說過他們，他們是在他們的途中！
I've given them as much time as I can, Mr. Hadden.
我已經給了他們足夠的時間，我可以，先生。哈登。
We can't wait any longer.
我們不能再等下去了。
- We're finished here. - Yes, sir.
- 我們在這里完成。 - 是的，先生。
Daddy!
爸爸！
I told you they'd make it.
我告訴你，他們會做吧。
I'm not re-calling the bombs
我不是回顧炸彈。
until I'm certain this thing works.
直到我敢肯定這件事情的作品。
Let's do this before it's too late.
讓我們這樣做之前，為時已晚。
The suit should protect you from the light.
西裝應該保護你從光。
It limits your exposure to any ionizing radiation,
它限制你接觸到的任何電離輻射，
but I can't make any promises.
但我不能做出任何承諾。
I don't actually know what's happening,
我真的不知道發生了什么，
but it seems that the vortex is dissipating
但似乎漩渦正在消退。
and the storm seems to be coming to an end!
和風暴似乎即將結束！
John.
約翰。
Oh, thanks.
哦，謝謝。
I think we need to get a drink.
我認為，我們需要喝一杯。
And when I say we I mean me.
當我說我們我的意思是我。
It's your round, professor.
這是你的回合，教授。
Are you ok, sir?
你怎么了，先生？
Call my doctor.
叫我的醫生。
Right away, sir.
馬上，先生。
- Colonel. - Yes?
- 上校。 - 是嗎？
If you could possibly help me with something...
如果你能可能幫助我的東西。
lf l can.
如果我可以。
Key Nine to Base, we're ready.
關鍵九基地，我們準備好了。
Alright, seal the chamber.
好吧，密封腔。
Copy that.
收到。
It's over.
結束了。
What now?
現在怎么辦？
One second.
等下。
Her father is dead.
她的父親已經死了。
Sienna, I'm so sorry.
西耶娜，我很抱歉。
It's ok, I guess I knew it was coming
沒關系，我想我知道這遲早要來。
I just didn't know when.
我只是不知道什么時候。
I understand.
我明白。
I guess you do,
我猜你做的，
more than anyone else.
比其他人多。
CMV has just learned that mysterious billionaire
CMV剛剛得知神秘的億萬富翁。
William Hadden has died.
威廉·哈登已經去世。
It is not known exactly when Mr. Hadden passed,
它不知道哈登先生確切死亡時間，
but his representatives say that it was some time last week.
但他的發言人說是上周某個時間。
Not since Howard Hughes has there been so much mystery
不是因為霍華德·休斯已經有這么多的奧秘。
surrounding the death of a billionaire.
周圍的億萬富翁死亡。
粗譯:賈寶玉是我龜孫子